Let's now go ahead and test to make sure that we can't enter the raffle whenever this raffle is not open or it's calculating.
让我们来测试一下，确保我们在未开放或是计算状态下确实是无法进入抽奖的
So we'll say it doesn't allow entrance, when raffle is Cal cumulating.
所以我们写 `it("doesnt allow entrance when raffle is calculating")`
And this will be an async function.
这里还是 `async function`
And first we'll enter will say await raffle dot enter raffle value is raffle entrance fee.
首先我们要写 `await raffle.enterRaffle()`
Now what we want to do we want to get this raffle into a closed state.
现在我们要让抽奖进入到关闭状态
So we want to get it out of its open state.
也就是我们想让它脱离开放状态
Well, how do we move this raffle from raffle dot open to raffle dot closed
那么我们该如何才能把抽奖从 "Raffle.OPEN" 转移到 "Raffle.CLOSE" 呢
in perform upkeep, remove the raffle from raffle that open to raffle dot calculating
在 "performUpkeep" 中，我们把抽奖从 "Raffle.OPEN" 转移到了 "Raffle.CALCULATING" 上
but perform upkeep can only be called if check upkeep returns true.
但 "performUpkeep" 只有在 "checkUpkeep" 返回 true 时才会被调用
Otherwise, it'll revert with raffle upkeep not needed.
否则它就会使用 "Raffle__UpkeepNotNeeded" 进行回滚
So what we need to do is we need to make check upkeep return true.
所以我们需要做的就是让 "checkUpkeep" 返回 true
And we will pretend to be the channeling keeper network
接着我们假装是 "Chainlink Keeper" 网络
to keep calling checkup keep waiting for it to be true.
去对 "checkUpkeep" 保持调用并等待它返回 true
And once we make it true, then we'll pretend to be the channeling keepers and call perform upkeep
一旦我们获得了 true，我们就假装成 "Chainlink Keepers" 去调用 "performUpkeep"
to put this contract in a state of calculating.
并把合约的状态改为 "CALCULATING"
Now how do we actually do that?
那我们该怎么做呢？
Well, in order for checkup keep to be true, we first need to see that we are indeed open,
嗯，为了让 "checkUpkeep" 为 true，首先就需要确保我们处于开放状态
which we are.
我们也的确是的
The next thing that we need to do though, is we need to do this time passed bit.
下一个需要做的是满足 "timePassed" 的要求
We need to actually wait that 30 seconds for time to pass.
我们需要等待 30 秒以通过这个时间
Now, that kind of sounds awful.
但这听起来有点扯啊
Do we have to wait 30 seconds for all of our tests?
难道我们必须要在所有测试中都等待 30 秒么？
What if our interval was 10 days
如果我们的 "interval" 是 10 天呢？
when we have to wait 10 days to run our tests?
我们就真在运行测试的时候等 10 天？
It sounds ridiculous.
这就有点搞笑了
Well, hard hat actually comes built in with a ton of functions for us to manipulate our blockchain to do literally whatever we want it to do.
实际上 hardhat 内置了大量的函数，让我们可以控制区块链以达到我们想要的目的
In the hard hat documentation.
在 hardhat 的文档中，
There's a section called Hard Hat Network reference inside the Hard Hat Network section.
有一个名为 "Hardhat Network Reference" 的部分，它在 "Hardhat Network" 部分里
And in here, there's a ton of information about how the hard hat network actually works and different configs that we can do with it.
这里有大量有关 Hardhat 网络如何运作以及我们能做哪些配置的信息
If we scroll down low enough, we can see the JSON RPC methods that we can use on this blockchain,
如果我们往下拉，就可以看到我们在链上用到的 "JSON-RPC methods"
we can do eath accounts block number call chinetti. We can do all these RPC methods that a normal blockchain has.
我们可以使用 "eth_accounts, blockNumber, call, chainId" 等所有一般区块链都具有的 "RPC" 方法
Additionally, we can do even more than that,
不止于此，我们还能做到更多的事情
we can use these things called Hard Hat Network methods.
我们还能使用这种被称为 "Hardhat network methods" 的方法
Since this is our local Hard Hat Network.
由于我们用的是本地的 Hardhat 网络
And we're using this for testing, we want to be able to test any scenario.
我们用它来进行测试，所以我们希望它在任何场景中都能够适用
And it's these methods that give us the ability to do that,
而正是这些方法赋予了我们这样的能力
you can go through this and play around and see all the different things you can do.
你可以浏览一下这里，看看都可以用到哪些不同的方法
One of them in particular is going to be set storage set where you can set storage at any place, which is really fun.
其中一个比较特殊的是这个 "setStorageAt" 通过它你可以把 "storage" 设置在任何地方，是一个很有趣的功能
But some of the special testing debugging methods are going to be EVM increase time, and EVM. Mine
还有一些比较特殊的测试调试方法，它们是 "evm_increaseTime" 以及 "evm_mine"
increased time allows us to automatically increase the time of our blockchain
"increaseTime" 能让我们自动增加我们区块链的时间
and EVM. Mine allows us to mine or create new blocks,
而 "evm_mine" 则可以让我们挖矿或者说创建一个新的区块
because if we increase the time, it doesn't do anything unless there's a new block mined.
因为如果我们增加了时间，除非有新的区块被挖出来，否则它不会产生任何影响
So what we can do is we can run a wait network,
所以我们可以这么写 `await network`
and we'll import network from Hard Hat Network
不过我们要先从 "hardhat" 中把 "network" 导入进来
await network dot provider that send EVM in crease time, comma,
`await network.provider.send("evm_increaseTime", )`
we can send a list of parameters to send with it, which for us are just going to be our interval.to number.
我们可以通过一个列表把参数发送过去，对我们来说就是 `interval.toNumber()`
And then we'll do plus one.
然后再加上一
Now right now, our interval isn't stored globally, so we're probably going to want to do
现在，我们的 "interval" 还没有全局存储，所以我们要处理一下
So let's go ahead and do interval.
所以我们先在这里写 `interval`
And then in our before each, we'll do interval equals await, raffle dot raffle dot get interval,
然后在我们的 "beforeEach" 中，我们执行 `interval = await raffle.getInterval()`
I'm just going to copy this and we're going to delete this whole line.
我直接从这里复制，然后把这一整行都删掉
Wait raffle dot get interval.
`await raffle.getInterval`
Since now we're just going to call it interval at a global level, since we're going to use it a lot.
现在我们就可以在全局层面调用 "interval" 了，我们会用到它很多次的
Now we're gonna say interval that to number plus one.
现在我们执行了 `interval.toNumber() + 1`
So we want to increase the time by whatever our interval is
我们想增加时间，无论我们的 "interval" 是多少
to make sure that we can actually get that checkup keep to return true.
目的是为了确保 "checkUpkeep" 可以持续地返回 true
So additionally, we're going to want to do a weight network dot provider. Dot send EVM mine with an empty array
此外，我们还要执行一个 `await network.provider.send("evm_mine")` 以及一个空的数组
just because we just want to mine it one extra block.
因为我们只是想要挖出一个额外的区块而已
You can also do network dot provider that request with an await here,
你也可以执行 `network.provider.request()` 前面还有一个 `await`
these two would be basically the same, but this one's a little quicker, right?
这两个基本上是一样 的，但这一个会快一些
So we've increased the time of our blockchain. We've mined a block to move forward.
现在我们已经为我们的区块链增加了时间，并向前挖了一个区块
It should be open time has passed.
"timePassed" 的要求应该是已经满足了
Do we have a player? We do indeed,
那我们有玩家么？确实是有的
because we've entered the raffle.
因为我们已经进入了抽奖
We should have a balance because we've entered the right Apple,
我们同样也有余额，还是因为我们已经进入了抽奖
check upkeep should now return true.
"checkUpkeep" 现在应该能返回 true 了
So we should be able to call perform upkeep and pretend to be a chain lock keeper.
所以我们应该已经能调用 "performUpkeep" 并假装成一个 "Chainlink Keeper" 了
So we're going to pretend to be a chain the keeper and call await raffle dot perform upkeep.
所以我们要假装成是一个 "Chainlink Keeper" 并调用 `await raffle.performUpkeep`
And we're going to pass this some empty call data just by passing a blank array like that.
然后我们要传入一个空的 "calldata" 也就是直接传入一个空的数组，就像这样
And now this should be in a calculating state.
现在，它应该就已经处于 "CALCULATING" 状态了
So now that it's in a calculating state,
由于我们已经在 "CALCULATING" 状态了
we can say our enter raffle reverts correctly if the raffle isn't open.
所以我们现在就可以说 "enterRaffle" 会正确地发生回滚，如果抽奖是未开放状态的话
So now we'll say await, expect raffle dot enter, raffle.
现在我们写 `await expect(raffle.enterRaffle())`
And we'll send it value of raffle entrance fee.
并且我们发送 `value: raffleEntranceFee`
We're expecting this.to dot b dot reverted with that raffle underscore underscore not open error.
我们期望发生的是 `.to.be.revertedWith("Raffle__NotOpen")`
Okay, let's try just this in our tests now.
OK，现在让我们来尝试一下我们的测试
So we'll run Hardhead test dash dash grep. Put this in quotes.
我们运行 `hh test --grep` 把它放进引号里
And perfect that passes as well.
完美，这个也通过了